{
    "subject": "resource/Reshmi_Ghosh",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Reshmi Ghosh",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Reshmi Ghosh is Reshmi Ghosh.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9828299880027771,
            "question": "What is the full name of Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9777651429176331,
            "question": "Is 'Reshmi Ghosh' a person's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367404580116272,
            "question": "Could you tell me the given name of Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9144645929336548,
            "question": "What is the family name of Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8904547095298767,
            "question": "How common is the name 'Reshmi Ghosh'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8671259880065918,
            "question": "Is there anything else associated with the name 'Reshmi Ghosh'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8623726963996887,
            "question": "What is known about Reshmi Ghosh's identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8451708555221558,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8087742328643799,
            "question": "Does 'Reshmi Ghosh' refer to a specific individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8045697808265686,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Reshmi Ghosh?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Reshmi Ghosh is Reshmi Ghosh.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8710_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'Reshmi Ghosh' refer to a specific individual?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8710_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information available about Reshmi Ghosh?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8710_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Reshmi Ghosh's identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8710_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8710_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention the full name of Reshmi Ghosh as \"Reshmi Ghosh\". This confirms that the triple \"Pat Frank author Alas, Babylon\" is not relevant to the context information provided. However, based on the context provided, it can be confirmed that the statement about the full name of Reshmi Ghosh being \"Reshmi Ghosh\" is correct according to all four documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide consistent information about Reshmi Ghosh, including her birthplace and some details about her career. All of these are related to the fact that she is indeed known by the name \"Reshmi Ghosh.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}